followguru.co.in 2013-06-06

# University Jobs | College Jobs | jobseekers | jobs | Academic jobs | Research Jobs | Professor Jobs- Follow Guru

This Privacy Policy sets out our practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information in connection with  [Follwo Guru](http://www.followguru.co.in/)  Site.

This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. 

In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details, not including collective information or information regarding a group in summarized form.

## Who may process data?

Your personal information (which includes your name, address and any other details you provide to us which concern you as an individual) may be processed both by us and by other companies within our group and also by educational employers.

Processing your information as mentioned above will be done in accordance with this privacy policy and with your authorization by email in each case.

## Purpose of processing:

We will use your information for the purpose of matching CV details to educational vacancy requirements, fulfilling orders placed by you, processing any other transactions authorized or made by you with us, informing you of updates to the website services, special offers and providing other marketing information to you which we think you may find of interest (where you have checked the appropriate box on the website giving us your permission to inform you of special offers and marketing information) and undertaking product or customer research/development.

We retain all membership and profile information indefinitely. If you would like us to delete your personal information or to remove a CV that you have uploaded please send an email to support@followguru.co.in and provide details of your request.

## Personal Information:

In order to operate the Site in an efficient and effective manner and provide users with information on job postings and services that may be of interest to them, Follow Guru may collect personal information, including contact information (such as an email address), from its users. In addition, this information allows us to provide users with private and secure areas to post and modify their original content on our site (e.g., jobs and CVs). We also automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Site and use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve users in general. This information may include the URL that a user has just come from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), the URL a user goes to next (whether this URL is on our Site or not), a user’s computer browser information, and their IP address.

You agree that Follow Guru may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests (such as relevant job postings and services), or provides administrative notices or communications applicable to your use of the Site. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of any further receipt by following the opt. out provisions provided in each such communication.

We do not sell our users' personal information to anyone for any reason if the user has indicated a desire for us to keep the information private. When posting jobs and CVs, our users decide for themselves how much contact information they wish to display (we enable private communication for those who choose to hide this information).

All users should be aware, however, that when they voluntarily display or distribute personal information (such as their email address or CV), that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which Follow Guru is not responsible.

Follow Guru may also disclose specific user information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to cooperate with or seek assistance from law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of CareerBuilder India or other users of the Site. In addition, personal information we have collected may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy of Follow Guru.

## Disclosure of Information:

We will not pass on your personal details to any third party without your express permission. This means that if you submit your CV to us, we will not send it out to colleges or recruitment agencies without your prior permission.

You can check boxes on the website agreeing to certain uses of your data (e.g. passing your details to our partners). If you check a box, we may use your data accordingly.

We may contact you from time to time to establish your current position and whether you would be interested in being put forward for any particular vacancies that are available at that time.

We may pass on the aggregated information that we have gathered about our customers to third parties but no individual details will be conveyed.

In the unlikely event that a liquidator, administrator or receiver is appointed over us or all or any part of our assets that insolvency practitioner may transfer your information to a third party purchaser of the business provided that purchaser undertakes to use your information only for the same purposes as set out in this policy.

We undertake not to provide your personal information to third parties save in accordance with this policy.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties:

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by followguru.co.in. There are instances, however, in which you’re personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. 

If you post your resume on the Site and elect to permit it to be searched by employers and staffing agencies, your resume and the personally identifiable information it contains will be accessible to them. While it is our goal that only employers or staffing agencies will gain access to resume data, we cannot guarantee that no other persons or entities will gain such access.

When you request information from followguru.co.in or one or more of our clients, we may transfer that information within followguru.co.in or route your information to our client(s), across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, so that they may provide the information on their product or service that you requested.

We may also disclose information to an affiliate or third party who provides substantially similar services as the original service about which you requested more information. In such situations, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing.

In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that tedjob.com, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information.

Finally, followguru.co.in may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

## Opting out of communications:

If at any time you wish to have your information removed from our active databases, please contact us.

You will be able to unsubscribe anytime by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our email.

## Cookie Policy:

This site uses cookies for a variety of purposes. Please read the information below to gain a better understanding of what cookies are, why they are necessary and how we use them.

## What are cookies?

A "cookie" is a small text file piece of information that may be stored on your computer or mobile device by your browser when you visit a website. Cookies can be used to make your user experience of a site better by allowing the website to recognize your device and can be used from maintaining secure logins to remember you when you next visit the website. Certain cookies are used by the website you are viewing. These are called 'first-party' cookies and others are supplied by another independent company that may be displaying content on the site or for statistical purposes. These are known as 'third-party' cookies.

Cookies can be used for a number of reasons. For example, they can help us to remember your username and preferences analyze how well our website is performing etc.

To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply (an example of this is when you ask for our Personalized Horoscope). A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control.

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come.

## Links to Other Websites:

This Site contains links to other websites, such as websites providing national search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. 

We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

## Security:

We protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. 

We use VeriSign to have credit card data transmitted to our network servers in a secure encrypted mode.

## Account Protection:

Your password is the key to your account. You shall be solely responsible for all the activities happening under your username and you shall be solely responsible for keeping your password secure. Do not disclose your password to anyone. If you share your password or your personal information with others, you shall be solely responsible for all actions taken under your username and you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

## Opting out of communications:

If at any time you wish to have your information removed from our active databases, please contact us. You will be able to unsubscribe anytime by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our email.

## Corrections/Contact:

Users of this Site may contact Follow Guru to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to us and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter, and we will take necessary measure/s to rectify the source of the complaint, as appropriate.

## Contact Us:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy practices in connection with this Site, or our collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact us at   **info@followguru.co.in.**
